Column description

- runtimeMinutes: 		Primary runtime of the title, in minutes. #25-75 percentile range for each titleType
- startYear: 			Represents the release year of a title. In the case of TV Series, it is the series start year. #to keep
- endYear: 			TV Series and TV mini series end year. #lets replace with startYear for now #probably to remove
- numRegions: 	 		The regions number for this version of the title. #to keep
- canHaveEpisodes:		Whether or not the title can have episodes. #keep for now
- totalCredits:			Total Number of Credits for the title. # to keep, test w/ both this and deltaCredits to compare results
- titleType:			The type/format of the title (e.g. movie, short, tvseries, tvepisode, video, etc). #to Keep
- ratingCount: 			The total number of user ratings submitted for the title. #to keep
- genres: 			The genre(s) associated with the title (e.g., drama, comedy, action). #to keep, think about how to encode it
- castNumber: 			Total Number of Cast individuals present within the IMDb title page. #bruno will keep it # Me and Chiara will remove it
- CompaniesNumber: 		Total Number of companies that worked for the title. #to keep
- averageRating:		Weighted average of all the individual user ratings. #to keep
- writerCredits:		Total number of writer credits of the title. #to keep as of now #we are checking
- directorCredits: 		Total number of director credits of the title. #to keep as of now #we are checking
- soundMixes:			Technical specification of the sound mixes available for the title. #to keep, think about how to encode it, treat the missing values


Added features:
- totalMedia:           Sum of totalImages, totalVideos, quotesTotal and externalLinks
- deltaCredits:         totalCredits - (castNumber + writerCredits + directorCredits) #TODO
- totalNominations:     awardWins + awardNominationsExcludeWins #TODO
- [regions/countryOfOrigin]_<continent>: number of countries for each continent
- [regions/countryOfOrigin]_freq_enc:    frequency encoding of one of the 2 features
- reviewsTotal:         userReviewsTotal + criticReviewsTotal